Week 16. Day 1. Dylan Thomas. Script. Talented. Asthma. Bronchitis. Prefer. Drop out of school.
Journalist. Fuse. Dominion. Volume. Publish. Smog. Pneumonia. Day 2. The Fall and Rise of Pompeii.
Thriving. Merchant. Fertile. Poisonous. Preserve. Mummy. Destination. Irony. Day 3. Alpacas. Alpaca.
Mass. Fluff. Dart. Slope. Startled. Altitude. Foothill. Hay. Herd. Camelirdy. Llama. Shade.
Chubby. Sheer. Day 4. American football. Gazelle. Smash. Touchdown. Go wild. Elsewhere.
Field. Rugby. League. Championship. Strategy. Root. Day 5. Cats. Lap. Purr. Need. Content.
Paw. Disgusted. Rear up. Hind. Curve. Swish. Indecisive. Aggressive. Wag. Flatten. Trusting.
Day 6. Social Contagion. Contagion. Cough. Keep from. Germ. State of being. Catching. Yawn.
Design. Imitate. Gain weight. Spouse. Sibling. Day 7. Raphlesia. The corpse flower. Raphlesia.
Corpse. Repulsive. Fowl. Stinking. Apply to. Rot. Flesh. Reddish. Wort. Pollinate. Pollen.
Reproduce. Genis. Untouched. Habitat.